Guide to the David Richmond Gergen Papers, 1964-1999 (bulk 1971-1992) RL.00443
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
David Richmond Gergen papers
1964-1999 (bulk 1971-1992)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Gergen, David R. (David Richmond), 1942-
RL.00443
216.7 Linear Feet
Counselor, special advisor, director of communications, and speech writer to U.S. Presidents Nixon, Ford, Reagan, and Clinton. Gergen has also worked as a journalist, serving as Editor-at-large of U.S. News and World Report and as a regular analyst on the "MacNeil/Lehrer NewsHour" and the "NewsHour with Jim Lehrer." A native of Durham, N.C., Gergen graduated from Yale University and the Harvard Law School and served for three-and-a-half years in the U.S. Navy. The collection includes materials from Gergen's career in politics as well as his journalism career. Among his political materials are presidential campaign materials for the 1972, 1976, 1980, and 1984 elections; subject files; office memos; chronological files and telephone logs; daily planners; and legal and financial papers; as well as drafts and transcripts of Gergen's and other's speeches. The collection includes 86 black-and-white and color photographs, 16 audio cassettes; and 106 video cassettes. Other materials document his journalism career, including editorials, interoffice memos, and other U.S. News and World Report documents; financial and subject files relating to his work as an analyst on the MacNeil/Lehrer NewsHour; speeches; correspondence, chronological files, and telephone logs; and financial papers. The addition contains 445 electronic computer files; 5 color and 40 black-and-white photographs; 16 slides; and 82 video cassettes; as well as 35 audio cassettes. The audio and video cassettes include interviews with Richard Nixon and Ross Perot.
121,428 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Also, some of the materials in this collection are not immediately accessible, because they require further processing before use.
All or part of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The David Richmond Gergen Papers was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2000.
Biographical Note
Chronology List
9 May 1942 Born in Durham, NC, to parents Aubigne Munger and Dr. John Jay Gergen
1963 B.A., Yale University
1967 LL.B., Harvard University
1967-1971 Officer, U.S. Navy
1971-1972 Staff Assistant, Nixon Administration
1973-1974 Special Assistant to President Richard Nixon
1975-1977 Special Counsel to President Gerald Ford
1977-1981 Resident Fellow, American Enterprise Institute
1981-1984 Director of Communications and Assistant to President Ronald Reagan
1985-1986 Editor, U.S. News and World Report
1985-2000 Contributor, The NewsHour with Jim Lehrer
1986- Editor-at-Large, U.S. News and World Report
1993-1994 Counselor to President Bill Clinton
1994 Special Advisor to President Bill Clinton and Secretary of State Warren Christopher
1995-1998 Visiting Professor, Duke University
1999- Prof. of Public Service, Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University
2000 Author, Eyewitness to Power: The Essence of Leadership from Nixon to Clinton (Simon and Schuster)
2000-2001 Commentator, ABC News Nightline
2000-2002 Moderator, World @ Large PBS discussion series
2000- Director, Center for Public Leadership, Kennedy School of Government
2002-2003 Commentator, Marketplace
Collection Overview
This collection (74,159 items, dated 1964-1999) documents David Gergen's professional life as a speech writer, director of communications, and special counsel for U.S. Secretary of the Treasury William E. Simon and for Presidents Nixon, Ford, and Reagan. The materials include presidential campaign materials for the 1972, 1976, 1980, and 1984 elections; subject files; office memos; chronological files and telephone logs; daily planners; and legal and financial papers; as well as drafts and transcripts of Gergen's and other's speeches. The collection includes 86 black-and-white and color photographs, 16 audio cassettes; and 106 video cassettes. (2000-0356)
The addition (47,269 items, dated 1987-1996) continues to document David Gergen's involvement in national politics, as both Counselor and Special Advisor to President Clinton from 1993 to 1995, and as a journalist. Materials include editorials, interoffice memos, and other U.S. News and World Report documents; financial and subject files relating to his work as an analyst on the MacNeil/Lehrer NewsHour; speeches; correspondence, chronological files, and telephone logs; and financial papers. The addition contains 445 electronic computer files; 5 color and 40 black-and-white photographs; 16 slides; and 82 video cassettes; as well as 35 audio cassettes. The audio and video cassettes include interviews with Richard Nixon and Ross Perot. (2000-0415)
Photographs; Videocassettes; Slides (photographs); Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1972; Elections -- United States; Presidents -- United States; Politics, Practical -- United States; United States -- Politics and government; Communication -- Political aspects -- United States; Speechwriters -- United States; Machine-readable records; Cabinet officers -- United States; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1984; Audiocassettes; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1980; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1976; Perot, H. Ross, 1930-; Reagan, Ronald; Gergen, David R. (David Richmond), 1942-; Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994; Simon, William E., 1927-; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Gergen, David R. (David Richmond), 1942-
- Accession (2000-0356)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  This collection is RESTRICTED: Researchers must obtain Gergen's permission before using any part of this collection.
  Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.
  - Speaking Engagement files,1982-1984 (Box 1)
    - National Journal Speech (Box 1)
    - Harvard/ABC Symposium, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Denver Trip (Box 1)
    - NYC Trip-MPA Speech, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Canada Vacation (Box 1)
    - St. Louis-Public Broadcasting System Speech (Box 1)
    - RR Korea and Japan Trip (Box 1)
    - Center for Study of the Presidency-Minneapolis, MN (Box 1)
    - New York City (Box 1)
    - Duke-Visitors Board (Box 1)
    - Pittsburgh-Business Professional Advertising Association (Box 1)
    - Washington-Center for Study of Presidency (Box 1)
    - Boston-Univ. of Massachusetts Medical Center (Box 1)
    - Boston (Box 1)
    - Chamber of Commerce and Harvard Law School Reunion (Box 1)
    - Gerald R. Ford Foundation/Grand Rapids, MI (Box 1)
    - Europe, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Gergen speeches and appearances,1981 March-1982 May (Box 2)
    - Baltimore-AAPOR (Box 2)
    - Washington-Georgetown University-Foreign Service (Box 2)
    - Chicago-American Society of Newspapers (Box 2)
    - Chicago (Box 2)
    - D.C.-National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences (Box 2)
    - National Home Builders Association Auxiliary (Box 2)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Washington Press Club (Box 2)
    - D.C.-CSIS Congressional Leadership (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Republican Senate News Secretary (Box 2)
    - D.C.-National Press Club (Box 2)
    - Duke University (Box 2)
    - D.C.-National Association of Government Communicators (Box 2)
    - University of Virginia (Box 2)
    - D.C.-The Executive Public Policy Insurance (Box 2)
    - Detroit-Newspaper Advertising Bureau Inc. (Box 2)
    - Durham-Duke University and Rotary Club (Box 2)
    - D.C.-National Capital Area Political Science (Box 2)
    - Hilton Head (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Credit Union National Association (Box 2)
    - D.C.-AEI Public Policy Research Panel (Box 2)
    - Business-Government Relations Council-Greenbrier (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Transamerica Corp. Management (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Washington Quarterly (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Young Presidents Organization (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Reporters Luncheon-National Press (Box 2)
    - Yorktown, Virginia (Box 2)
    - D.C.-McLean Business and Professional Association (Box 2)
    - D.C.-AAAA's Convention (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Foreign Student Service Council (Box 2)
    - D.C.-National Urban Coalition (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Brookings Institute (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Washington Center for Learning Alternatives (Box 2)
    - AAPOR Speech D.C.-National Foreign Policy Conference (Box 2)
    - Washington-Proctor and Gamble Co. (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Edison Electric Institute Seminar (Box 2)
    - D.C.-Mutual Broadcasting System Inc. (Box 2)
    - NYC-American Political Science Association Conference (Box 2)
    - Durham-Duke University Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs Meeting (Box 2)
    - NYC-13-15 March (Box 2)
    - Washington-American University Seminar (Box 2)
    - Washington-Bendix Corp. Industrial Group (Box 2)
    - Washington-Foreign Press Center (Box 2)
    - Yale-Roper Center Spring Board Meeting (Box 2)
    - D.C.-American Academy of Political and Government Studies Seminar (Box 2)
    - D.C.-AEI Executive Seminar (Box 2)
    - MISC. Groups DG met with (informal speeches, etc.), 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous Speech (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
    - Letter of Resignation,1983, from Gergen toReagan and from Reagan to Gergen (Box 3)
    - Ford vs.Carter Debate Issues (Box 3)
    - Audiotapes (Box 3)
    - Chautauqua Cassette Program,1989 (Box 3)
    - Japan, China in Change (Box 3)
    - CLSC Sidewalk Session (Box 3)
    - Videotapes
      - MacNeil/Lehrer Productions,1990, 3 copies (Box 3)
      - Crossfire,1982 (Box 3)
      - Ben Wattenberg at Large:Reagan's America (Box 3)
      - ABC News Special - JFK (Box 3)
    - Professional Appointment Book,1981 (Box 3)
    - Professional Appointment Book,1982 (Box 3)
    - Professional Appointment Book,1983 (Box 3)
  - Videotapes,1988-2000 (Box 4)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer, 2 copies? (Box 4)
    - America 2000 Satellite Town Meeting #5,1992 (Box 4)
    - The Fourth Annual Report of the Secretaries of Defense: The Iraqi Crisis (Box 4)
    - C-SPAN Viewer Call-in,1991 (Box 4)
    - Vanderbilt University - America 2000: Toward A Learning Community (Box 4)
    - Prime Time Live,1990 (Box 4)
    - "New Congress/New President" (Box 4)
    - Ross Perot - An American Profile,1992 (Box 4)
    - In Search of the Real America: The Enemies of Growth,1978 (Box 4)
    - In Search of the Real America: Pig of the World,1977 (Box 4)
    - American Political Parties Part II - The Republicans: Before and AfterReagan,1988 (Box 4)
    - "Dads Tape Only" (Box 4)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer,1990 (Box 4)
    - WRI - Global Environment (Box 4)
    - Wolanchuk Report,1990 (Box 4)
    - U.S. News and World Report: The Wing,1988 (Box 4)
    - U.S. News and World Report: Second Home,1988 (Box 4)
    - The Republicans: Before and AfterReagan,1988 (Box 4)
    - WNET,1989 (Box 4)
    - Harvest of Despair (Box 4)
    - Media Relations - "Cross of Fire" - Part I,1989 (Box 4)
    - Prime Time,1990 (Box 4)
    - George Marshall and the American Century (Box 4)
    - The Republicans (Box 4)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer - Museum of Broadcasting (Box 4)
    - "Dad's Tape" (Box 4)
    - "Dad's Tape Only" (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Files (Box 5)
    - Notes on Meetings (Box 5)
    - "Miscellaneous Notes", 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Resumes and Letters (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Letters of Application, Carbon Copies (Box 5)
    - Biographical (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Financial Statements, 4 folders (Box 5)
    - Long Range Planning Meeting/Labor Day (Box 5)
    - James A. Baker Speech,1981 (Box 5)
    - Political Alignment (Box 5)
    - Stockman Briefing (Box 5)
    - Herrington (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Personal financial information (Box 6)
    - Transactions, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Receipts
      - Hotel/travel (Box 6)
      - Meals/entertainment (Box 6)
      - Mags./books/misc. (Box 6)
    - IRA, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Taxes, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Paine Webber Transactions (Box 6)
    - DG Investments: Annuities Acct. (Box 6)
    - Charles Schwab Co. (Box 6)
    - Investment Transactions, 7 Folders (Box 6)
    - Taxes, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - "Tax Payer Copies" (Box 6)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 7)
    - Children's Letters (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Chron,1981 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Notes from DG Desk (Box 7)
    - Notes from DG Desk,1981 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Articles (Box 7)
    - Sears Roebuck vs. Ten Federal Agencies - News clippings (Box 7)
    - J.C. Penney Grand Jury Subpoena,1977 (Box 7)
    - 1979 Annual Meeting (Box 7)
    - Library Photocopying in the United States (Box 7)
    - Libraries, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Sample Press Kit (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Sample Press Kit (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - "Viewpoints: The Presidency: The Power and Glory," ed. Mary Klein (Box 7)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 8)
    - DG-Library Commission Notes and Records,1974-1979 (Box 8)
    - J.C. Penney Legal Files-ComPACT v. W. Michael Blumenthal, Vol. I,1979 (Box 8)
    - J.C. Penney Legal Files-ComPACT v. W. Michael Blumenthal, Vol. II,1979 (Box 8)
    - J.C. Penney Legal Files-ComPACT v. W. Michael Blumenthal, Vol. III,1979 (Box 8)
    - Edited Quotations from Gov.Jimmy Carter,1976, notebook, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - DG Copy of Pres. Ford's Briefing Book, Illinois Campaign Stop Q & A,1976 (Box 8)
    - Photocopies of Magazine, Newspaper, UPI and Reuters Reports on Changes in Pres. Ford's PR Staff,1976 (Box 8)
    - Republican National Convention Notebook,1976 (Box 8)
    - DG Copy of Pres. Ford's Debate Briefing Book (Economic Issues),1976 (Box 8)
    - DG Copy of VP Nom. Dole's Briefing Book, VP Debate,1976, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - DG Copy of Pres. Ford's Briefing Book, Press Conference,1976 (Box 8)
    - DG Copy of Pres. Ford's Briefing Book, Press Conference,1976 (Box 8)
    - DG Notes on VA, NC, SC State Campaigns,1976 (Box 8)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 9)
    - Issues - 1980 GOP Convention
      - Articles and Notes on 1980 Campaign Issues, Notes for Speeches (Box 9)
      - GeorgeBush - Vice President,1980 (Box 9)
      - DG File on VP Nom.George Bush,1980 (Box 9)
    - 1980 Republican National Convention (Box 9)
    - Misc. Personal Financial and Travel Records,1979-1980 (Box 9)
    - New York World Press Review Startup,1977 (Box 9)
    - Notes on Federal Budget, Immigration,1977 (Box 9)
    - Clippings on The Washington Star and The Washington Post,1977 (Box 9)
    - John Warner for US Senate (VA)-Campaign Materials,1978 (Box 9)
    - Janeway Materials,1978 (Box 9)
    - Rep. Otis Pike Resignation Speechtypescript, 1978 (Box 9)
    - DG Notes, Drafts for Speeches forRonald Reagan,1980 (Box 9)
    - William E. Simon, Radio, TV Scripts, Misc. Speeches, Articles,1979-1980 (Box 9)
    - William E. Simon, Notes, Drafts, Speeches, Articles,1980 (Box 9)
    - William E. Simon, Letter to Set Up Meeting with Puerto Rican Businessmen,1980 (Box 9)
    - DG USA Contacts, Inc., Speaking Engagement,1980 (Box 9)
    - DG University Club "Lunch Bunch" Speaking Engagement, 1980 (Box 9)
    - US Census Material,1979-1980 (Box 9)
    - DG Inner Council Organization of Capitol Hill Speaking Engagement,1979 (Box 9)
    - DG US Youth Council Speaking Engagement,1980 (Box 9)
    - DG Notes, Speech for Dinner held for Sen. Jesse Helms,1977 (Box 9)
    - Gerald Ford, Notes, Drafts, Speeches,1977-1978, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 10)
    - Bob Dole, memoranda,1978-1980 (Box 10)
    - Elizabeth Dole, Invitation, Speeches,1978 and undated (Box 10)
    - Speech given by Barbara Franklin, draft,1977 (Box 10)
    - DG Invitation to National Journal Lecture Series,1979 (Box 10)
    - House Judiciary Committee Hearings, Unedited Stenographic Minutes, Evening Session (copy),1974 (Box 10)
    - House Judiciary Committee Hearings, Unedited Stenographic Minutes, Afternoon Session (copy),1974 (Box 10)
    - DG Copy, Pres.Nixon's Briefing Book, "Domestic Issues,"1972 (Box 10)
    - State-by-State Profiles,1976 (Box 10)
    - DG Copy of Pres. Ford's Briefing Book, "Economic Issues,"1976 (Box 10)
    - DG Copy of Pres. Ford's Briefing Book, "Domestic Issues,"1976 (Box 10)
    - Ford Issues Book,1976, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Carter on the Issues,1976 (Box 10)
    - DG Speech, "American Attitudes Toward Government,"1980 (Box 10)
    - DG Writings,1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - DG Copy ofRonald Reagan's Briefing Book,1980 (Box 10)
    - Extra Copies of DG Speeches, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - DG Speeches,1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials. (Box 11)
    - DG Speeches,1979-1980, 10 folders (Box 11)
    - Strategy for the 80s-New Jersey Bell (Box 11)
    - DG Conferences and Meetings,1978 (Box 11)
    - Recordings of DG Speeches,1979 and undated (Box 11)
    - DG Public Policy Debates,1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - DG Notes, Speeches,1980 (Box 11)
    - DG McDonald's Speaking Engagement,1980 (Box 11)
    - DG Misc. Speeches,1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - DG American Political Science Association Speaking Engagement,1980 (Box 11)
    - DG Notes for Speech,1980 (Box 11)
    - DG Speech, Congressional Quarterly Forum on Political Polls,1980 (Box 11)
    - George Bush, Misc. Articles,1980 (Box 11)
    - George Bush Campaign, Los Angeles Times Article,1980 (Box 11)
    - 1980 Republican National Convention
      - GOP Convention News Clips (Box 11)
      - Campaign Facts (Box 11)
      - RNC Polling Materials (Box 11)
      - DG Bibliography (Box 11)
      - Ronald Reagan, Panama Canal Issue,1977 (Box 11)
      - Economy File (Box 11)
      - SALT File (Box 11)
      - Donald Rumsfeld File (Box 11)
      - Reagan Tax Program File (Box 11)
      - Federal Budget File (Box 11)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 12)
    - Maine briefing,1979 (Box 12)
    - Bush Townhouse (Box 12)
    - Schedule,1979, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Bush Luncheon, Hartford Hilton, Ford and Pearl St.,1979 May 1 (Box 12)
    - Maffitt, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - George Bush, Meet the Press,1979 April 6 (Box 12)
    - Humes (Box 12)
    - Houston Trip,1979 February 5 (Box 12)
    - Bush, Speech, Georgetown,1979 January 25, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Lindblom Book (Box 12)
    - Bush, Rec.1979 January 26. (Box 12)
    - "Reassessing the Crisis of Confidence," by Arthur H. Miller (Box 12)
    - Bush, Clips (Box 12)
    - Simon, Scripts, Standard Simon Speech, A Time for Truth. Simon speeches while Secretary of Treasury,1980 (Box 12)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 13)
    - Memoranda and Policy Papers,1981 (Box 13)
    - Press Kits,1981 (Box 13)
    - Gergen/Bush Update (Box 13)
    - Polling (Box 13)
    - DG Articles of Interest (Box 13)
    - Bush, Maine Position Papers (Box 13)
    - Wall Street Journal Interview with GeorgeBush (Box 13)
    - Iran (Box 13)
    - General Correspondence Re: Campaign1980 (Box 13)
    - US Economic Issues and the 1980 Presidential Candidates (prepared by Wm. F. Monroe&Assoc) (Box 13)
    - General Election, 1980 [includes folder titled William F. Ahlstron, A Proposed Reagan 'Shadow Govt.'] (Box 13)
    - Ronald Reagan Speeches as Presidential Candidate (Box 13)
    - Material Prepared for President Ford's Speech to the Council of Michigan Foundations, and Material Prepared for GeorgeBush 1979 March 1 (Box 13)
    - Bush Q and A's (Box 13)
    - Draft of Book byGeorge Bush (Never Published),1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield Correspondence (Box 13)
    - DRG, W.P. Article,Financial World, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Citation to David Gergen, Appointed to the Committee on Communications of the Republican National Committee,1978-1979 (Box 13)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 14)
    - Voluntarism (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous Speeches (Box 14)
    - American Federation of Women's Clubs (Box 14)
    - Bill Simon Speeches for Fall1980 (Box 14)
    - ABC Speech File (Box 14)
    - Future Articles (Box 14)
    - CIA Film Project (Box 14)
    - Latin America (Box 14)
    - DRG Article: Regulation (Box 14)
    - [David Gergen notes?], 5 folders (Box 14)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 14)
    - Constitutional Amendment (Box 14)
    - Jackie (Box 14)
    - Richard Cheney Fundraiser,1978 (Box 14)
    - Steve Syms,1980 (Box 14)
    - Smith-Kline Corporation (Box 14)
    - National Polls (Box 14)
    - Gary Jones, MacArthur Foundation (Box 14)
    - Department of the Treasury and The Sindlinger Report,1977-1979 (Box 14)
    - George Bush, South Carolina Trip and Debate (Box 14)
    - Dave Gergen, Issues File (Box 14)
    - Articles and Speeches by Senator Patrick Moynihan,1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Bush Issues, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 15)
    - Handwritten fundraising letter (Box 15)
    - Bush issues, 5 folders (Box 15)
    - Foreign policy and defense files,1979, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Public policy week (Box 15)
    - DG notes (Box 15)
    - Bush, Stef Halper (Box 15)
    - Issues - Papers and Coordination (Box 15)
    - Bush - people interested (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 15)
  - Pre-Reagan files and materials (Box 16)
    - Bush - China Article Washington Post (Box 16)
    - Other Candidates (Box 16)
    - Press Clips Of Interest (Box 16)
    - Bush - Issues And Answers (Box 16)
    - Themes (Box 16)
    - George Bush - Clips (Box 16)
  - Video tapes (includes network appearances) (Box 16)
  - Fellows of the Yale Corporation,1977-1998, color photo (Box 17)
  - Office Files (Box 17)
  - Taxes,1986 (Box 17)
  - Finances / Checks deposited,1986 (Box 17)
  - Directories --mailing and invitation lists, 5 folders (Box 17)
  - WP/LAT piece onBush's start,1989 March 5 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence re: The Washington Campus and Center for Democracy, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Clippings (Box 17)
  - Grossman project, correspondence, notes, and drafts, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - DG messages,1988 February-1988 August, 6 folders (Box 17)
  - Correspondence to and from Stephen Smith,1998 (Box 17)
  - Nightline transcript with Roone Arledge, 1988 (Box 17)
  - DG projects,1989 (Box 17)
    - Clippings (Box 17)
    - Cosby Bureau (Box 17)
    - Role of the Press Secretary by DG (Box 17)
    - Washington Report (Box 17)
    - Yale Club membership information and correspondence (Box 17)
    - TV show1989, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Ward Chamberlin Project,1989 (Box 17)
    - LA Times article: Tower Aftermath,For Nominees, Old Senate Rules still Apply (Box 17)
    - Contract for serving as panelist on Newsbreakers (Box 17)
    - Bush's second honeymoon WP/LAT (Box 17)
    - Triumvirate Piece (Box 17)
    - Bohemian Grove Cabin (Box 17)
  - DG Special interest,1988 (Box 17)
    - Letter toBush/USIA/Congrats, 1988 (Box 17)
    - General articles and reports (Box 17)
  - DG,1989Investments (Box 17)
  - Visa Receipts and Statements,1987 - 1989, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Thank you notes, resumes received by DG,1989, folders (Box 17)
  - Expense reports,1988-1989, 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Resumes received by DG, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - White House news summary,1984 February, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Faxes from Department of State, news highlights,1984 February, 2 folders (Box 18)